

EMMANUEL O. ESEIGBE

Personal Information

Address

No 28, Titilayo Jeta Avenue Ayobo Lagos

Phone 09030381626

Email

manugtech@gmail.com

State of Origin

Edo State

Date of Birth

25-04-1995

Marital Status

Single

Additional Skills

- HTML 5
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- WORDPRESS
- PYTHON/DJANGO

Professional Summary

Full Stack Web Developer specializing in front end development and Back end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, and Django. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Work Experience

06/2022 - Present

Anchorsoft Academy

- Train students on front-end and back-end development
- Help students ensure they acquire the appropriate skill required to handle a live project.
- Product development

02/2017 - 02/2022

Highcrown Digital Hub

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop projects concepts with WordPress and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior WordPress developers to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

Education

2014 - 2018

Oduduwa University

BSc. Computer Science

2005 - 2011

Fluorescent Group of Schools

Senior Secondary School Certificate

1999-2005

Ebun Oluwa Nursery and Primary School

Primary School Certificate

References

Martins Osadebey from Printsmart NG 08025257425